<Document>
# United Soviet Socialist Planets Lore Summary


Hailing from the planet of [bold]Nova Cygni[/bold], the [bold][color=brown]USSP[/bold][/color], or the [bold][color=brown]United Soviet Socialist Planets[/bold][/color],
emerged onto the galactic sphere as a fierce industrial superpower and a population that
passionately supports worker's rights and economic equality. The [bold][color=brown]USSP[/bold][/color] controls many
system territories and sports one of the most formidable navies in the galaxy, with
countless ships and men loyal to the Soviet cause. Alongside the [bold][color=cyan]TSF[/bold][/color] and the [bold][color=#8B0000]The Phaethon Dynasty[/bold][/color], they are recognized among the major factions vying for control of the esoteric
[bold][color=047ABD]Monolith[/bold][/color] and its bountiful resources.

<Box>
[bold][color=brown]"By sickle, hammer, and rifle, slaughtered is the pig."[/bold][/color]
</Box>

With a preference for longevity and production-efficiency in their weapons and technology, much [bold][color=brown]USSP[/bold][/color] technology has been reused with
little modification for decades, with some of their ship models even hailing from the early
spacefaring age. Some would call their tech outdated and ineffective, but the Soviets
champion its undeniable durability, lasting usefulness, and high production value, making
the [bold][color=brown]USSP[/bold][/color] an industrial core for mass-produced goods. This economic and technological
doctrine extends to their warfare strategy: cost efficiency and mass deployment, taking
over their enemies with sheer firepower and massive numbers. The [bold][color=brown]USSP[/bold][/color] commander in
chief, who acts as the executive authority of the [bold][color=brown]USSP[/bold][/color] beyond its home planet, is known
as the [bold]Autarch[/bold], and he rules his territory behind a mask of red and with a fist of iron. The
[bold]Autarch[/bold] enforces a political doctrine of loyalty for the Soviet cause (of expansion and the
spread of socialist ideals) and the destruction of the capitalist blot in all of its media. The
military uses a commisar system, with military commanders and leaders being tasked to
ensure complete and earnest loyalty to the [bold][color=brown]USSP[/bold][/color], both in affiliation and political and moral beliefs.

</Document>
