<Document>
  # Asakim

  Asakim are abandoned pre-fracture genetically enhanced reptillian bioweapons, they are remnants of long-gone wars, only woken up after extreme circumstances causing them to have a [color=red]cryostasis failure[/color] near the Colossus Sector.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MobAsakim"/>
  </Box>

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingOuterHardsuitAsakim"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponRifleAsakimAutopulser"/>
  </Box>

  ##As an Asakim:
  - You generally have no modern knowledge (maybe basic at most) of the sector and its inhabitants. You don't speak Andromeda Standard, and you shouldn't know about the culture of the TSF, PDV, or other factions.
  - Your goal is to secure territory and establish a base of operations in the absence of a chain of command.
  - Should you find stolen pre-fracture technology, you may reclaim it by force.
  - [bold]Your specialized gear is incredibly [color=#00CCFF]valuable and rare[/color], you should never give it up.[/bold]
  - [color=green]Civilians (Non-Faction) are not your enemy[/color], and can be bartered with if you can get past the language barrier.

  [color=#00FFCC][bold][italic]Fight with honor, prevent harm to the innocent, and destroy anything that stands in your path.[/italic][/bold][/color]

  ##Species Notes:
  [bold]As a genemodded trained bioweapon, you'll find that:[/bold]
  - Your highly developed lungs give you additional powerful melee damage, and claws inject 1u of [color=orange]Gastrotoxin[/color] on hit.
  - Your thick scales protect you more than they normally would.
  - Your additional eyes grants you basic biological nightvision.
  - You are generally bulkier than most, and have more power to drag things around.
  - Your heart is capable of processing up to 5 reagents at once.

  ## Misc Notes:
  - Asakim are generally undiscovered to the sector, and should not be commonly known IC.
  - [color=red][bold]Like Chimeras, you are not immune to safezone rules as an Asakim.[/bold][/color]
  - Asakim are hostile towards Factions and do not require escalation to attack or be attacked.
  - You are allied with the Remnant ADS ships and are expected to follow the orders of ADC AI units.
  - Stolen pre-fracture technology includes items and devices [bold]only[/bold] accessible through pre-fracture tech disks or theft, such as MS-250/500 Shield Generators and Curio-class ship weaponry. Research-tree technology such as CTLA-50s do not qualify as stolen technology.

</Document>
