<Document>
# TSFMC

  The [color=cyan]Trans-Solarian Federation Marine Corps[/color], the space-ground fighting force for the TSF, is one of the primary actors in the Colossus Sector. This brigade-level detachment has been deployed to Colossus in the interest of keeping the peace, although their constant conflicts with insurgent cells, pirates, and the local Phaethon Dynasty speak otherwise. Their natural militant approach and tendency to overhanded brute force methods have painted them as invaders to the locals who side with the Dynasty, the 'rightful rulers of the sector.'

  The [color=cyan]TSFMC[/color] detachment is backed by powerful futuristic technology, their gear favoring durable equipment and heavier weapons such as pulse lasers.
  However, they are at an extreme disadvantage due to being separated from reinforcements by interference from the monolithic region and the many AI drones corrupted by the [color=pink]local anomalous emissions[/color].
  Because of this, the TSFMC marines are in a defensive position, forced to use local resources and strategies varying from their training or risk being picked off by their enemies.

  The detachment's overall objectives, as briefed by High Command before deployment to the Colossus sector, are to:

  > Confiscate and study Corporate-war era technology wielded by the locals

  > Eliminate opposition and establish control over the sector for the TSF

  Detailed objectives for the everyday marine will be outlined by the commanding officer in charge as situations unfold, but with the detachment largely cut off from High Command and the outer sectors of TSF space, the overall task is clear: survival. Marines might very well be called upon to fend off anomalous threats, collect resources from debris and detritus, and study any relevant technology to strengthen their local military. Only through discipline and following the Chain of Command can a marine expect to thrive in this unforgiving sector.

# The Chain of Command

  The [color=gold][bold]Chain of Command[/bold][/color] is a tool to keep order and discipline in the TSFMC, but it is not a weapon to brutalize your fellow marines. Follow it, obey orders, and treat your fellow marines with respect, no matter if they are above you, the same rank as you, or below you. The CoC is made up of, in order of authority, Colonels, Captains, Fireteam Leaders, Marines (of multiple roles), and Cyborgs.

  The [color=gold]Colonel[/color] is the Commanding Officer (CO) and ultimate authority in the sector for the TSF, answering only to TSFMC High Command. The overall goals and objectives of the detachment as well as forward-facing diplomacy falls under their purview. Most tasks will be delegated to their Captains, who will delegate it to the FTLs. While they may personally head operations themselves, commanding a vessel and soaring into the fray, Colonels who do so often don't return and become a detriment to the operation as a whole.
  Keep in mind the realities your troops fight against as well — while you may be in charge, you are responsible for your marines' safety and success, and for their failures and deaths.

  The [color=cyan]Captain[/color] is the Executive Officer (XO) of the detachment and right hand of the Colonel. Their job entails taking the directives laid down by the Colonel and breaking them down into detailed objectives for the Fireteams under their battalion. They may also be an experienced officer in combat, able to head out into the fray to personally oversee operations as needed.

  [color=silver]Fireteam Leaders[/color] live on the front line with the marines under their command and are directly responsible for the training and real-time organization of their fireteam in battle, be it in space or on the ground. They are a marine's closest connection to detachment command, and as such FTLs should be in constant communication with their marines. FTLs answer to the Captain and command their own fireteam, assigned either by their superiors or handpicked from among the unassigned marines.

  [color=yellow]Marines[/color] answer to every high-ranking officer and fall into multiple roles of equal position: Marines, Corpsmen, and Engineers.
  Marines are the front line soldiers, existing to follow the orders of their superiors and to live or die for the glory of the Federation. They are assigned into Fireteams, and conduct boarding operations, extract technology, and do typical grunt combat work.

  [color=red]Corpsmen[/color] are specialized marines, acting as medical professionals in times of combat. If a marine is wounded, a Corpsman is the one to keep them alive. Their goal is to preserve the lives of other marines, but they aren't afraid to shoot some rounds themselves.

  [color=orange]Engineers[/color] are also specialized marines, prioritizing repairs and modifications to existing ships, handling logistics, and creating fortifications. If a ship has half its hull gone from a railgun shot, Engineers are the ones to make it seem like the ship came right from the drydock.

  [color=gray]Cyborgs[/color] are AI-controlled constructs, the latest advancement of superior Federation technology. They answer to their Federation Laws and any other TSFMC personnel.

# Gear

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponDEWCalico"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponRifleAnnie"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponEnergyRevolver"/>
  </Box>

  The TSFMC use a variety of weapons in ground combat, usually wielding state-of-the-art yet fickle energy weapons, advanced rifles, high-caliber SMGs, and plasma melee equipment.

  [color=green]Strengths:
  - TSFMC weapons are capable of dealing significant amounts of damage in a quick period of time.
  - Energy weapons are often easy to charge or reload, with most of their material investment being initial production.
  - Their advanced equipment has many different additional functions, ranging from EMP protection to additional ammo storage.
  - Energy weapons are able to pierce through glass - if you can see something, you can shoot it.

  [color=red]Weaknesses:
  - Like most of their gear, the TSFMC's energy weapons are vulnerable to high-strength EMP attacks, discharging their batteries.
  - Their heavier weapons are not good for quick responses - tight corridors will lead to a fast downfall without preperation.
  - While their weapons are powerful, they can each be countered through specific items - vary your loadout or stay with your squad.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingOuterHardsuitM82c"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingOuterHardsuitM86"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingOuterHardsuitNfsdExperimental"/>
  </Box>

  The TSFMC use heavy power armor for boarding operations, with more advanced equipment sacrificing base statistics for additional combat features.

  [color=green]Strengths:
  - TSFMC armor is durable and effective. With the right selection of gear, a marine can become nigh invincible.
  - Higher-level armor feature more perks and additions allowing for better adaptivity in combat, such as energy shields and optical enhancements.

  [color=red]Weaknesses:
  - Like most of their gear, some TSFMC armors are vulnerable to high-strength EMP attacks, discharging their shield capacitors.
  - While durable, their armor is quite heavy, reducing wearer maneuverability in combat and becoming a nuisance outside of it.

</Document>
