<Document>
# Phaethon Dynasty Lore Summary

[bold][color=#D2B48C]The Phaethon Dynasty[/bold][/color] is a dynasty forged from the crucibles of ruin.

Long since the shattering of the Syndicate in the [color=yellow][bold]First and Last Corporate War[/color][/bold], and longer since the galaxy-spanning dominions of the ancient past, [bold][color=#D2B48C]The Phaethon Dynasty[/bold][/color] has the scars of hardship imbedded into it's blood;
Formed by the fuedal enclaves that once inhabitted the perseus arm, on the frontier of the unexplored abyss [bold][color=#D2B48C]The Phaethon Dynasty[/bold][/color] was founded from the religious reverence for their leaders, a isolationist society arose, for where the Sultan reigned supreme. The remnant remains of the once glorious syndicate had been discovered in their expanding outer territories, to which inspired awe in the sultanate; technological findings beyond their greatest capabilties.
The Dynasty did not wait in veneration upon the discovery of their newly founded predecessors, they harvested the vicera of the corporation entities of old, redeveloping long abandoned industry for the prosperity of their dynasty. Technological power never harness before in the outer rim.
However the Dynasty was not without it's faults, the discovery of unknown technologies did not matter for the dynasty faced plagues, argriculture shortages, genetic and limitations, their isolation was their downfall. These issues had ravaged their territories throughout the generations. The difficulties they faced, while scarring of their populace - ultimately led to a robust society familiar with destitution.
Taking up residence in planetary systems surrounding the now-infamous Colossus sector, the growing populace of starved but hardy militants began to rebuild and regrow, ultimately forming a dynasty off of their now-ancient military ranking - [bold][color=#D2B48C]The Phaethon Dynasty[/bold][/color].

Due to their proximity, [bold][color=#D2B48C]The Phaethon Dynasty[/bold][/color] was the first political power to find the intense anomalies of the Colossus sector, and the first to enhance it's phenomenon. They were the first to coin its common term - "The Monolith".
Such grand phenomenon was not ignored by the other galactic governments, however...
While the [bold][color=#D2B48C]Dynasty[/bold][/color] has had times of instability and shaky future, it has persisted for over a century. Many of its citizens know little of its origins, but all share an unanimous hatred for foreign nations such as the Trans-Solarian Federation instilled through generations of isolationist teachings.
It is thus little surprise that when the TSF reared their heads and reached their hands to claim the wonders and horrors of the Colossus sector, [bold][color=#D2B48C]The Phaethon Dynasty[/bold][/color] formed shakey alliances, armed their civilians and readied their weapons for a war to come.

Despite this unity through the Sultanate, the [bold][color=#D2B48C]Dynasty[/bold][/color] is not perfect; Since the recent rediscovery of the lives of those outside their homelands, many in the [bold][color=#D2B48C]Dynasty[/bold][/color] are torn between fundamental old world beliefs from the history their Syndicate predessors with their religious teachings, and the promises and truthes revealed by the
outside sectors. This looming threat of another bloody schism hangs over the throne, but in the time of war, strong leaders know the cost of letting down their guard.

Much of the [bold][color=#D2B48C]Dynasty[/bold][/color]'s military-industrial complex stems from refineries and industrial equipment from long dead syndicate, but since reconnection with the rest of the galaxy, black-market trading has become their strongest economic niche - both in exports of illegal luxury goods from
outside the Colossus sector, to exports of preserved "syndicate" technology and data from the Monolith's anomalies.

Guerrilla strikes, AI corruption, propaganda floods, and sabotage operations leave the TSF
scrambling to take control of [bold]The Colossus Sector[/bold]. Their tactics are as much ideological as they are military, they indoctrinate and employ smaller foreign forces to fight with their elite-operative Vanguard forces, embracing the controversial techniques of the past and new, bringing even experienced enemies to their knees.
With neural leaks, anti-propaganda broadcasts, and liberated mythologies, [bold][color=#D2B48C]The Phaethon Dynasty[/bold][/color] exploits corruption, sabotages foreign relations and spreads rebellion in the Federation like a virus, harnessing their own knowledge of its societal shortcomings to cut it down. Their stations, scattered across the galactic arm, have remained graced with the weapons and indsutry of
their predecssors, making them a uncrushable infestation even for the Tran-Solar Federation.


</Document>
